{
    "id": "ab1b4f72f205406582e2350f43f2883a",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We eat that we ……………….. live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f166dddc143f4129a9f46f33dc5d93d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She worked hard that she ..................... win the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54e6538a349748a3b7fb375c97f76173"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………. go only if you have the permission.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "614515be11ab4f96ae090883bdcfc44d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked whether dinner ………………….. be ready soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0bfe720a4a804491b003b94f3d3bbe33"
        },
        {
            "question": "Even if you paid me to do so, I …………………. not support you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b4e36c166554e54a8b6a2151a7c716d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………….. go out provided that you return soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "will",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "727ae46a7da541d3b1d72e3845717f29"
        },
        {
            "question": "You make such a noise that I ………………….. work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cannot",
                "could not",
                "would not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "09b0d4ab962043048219c95d11e88a33"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ………………… try again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dec2243d01fb48a8afcebe2d01d895ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thieves stole whatever they …………………. find in the house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7fbbcc59f898467f8ceb7ac60b32e9f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… I carry this bag?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would",
                "Will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "259c3d463278484aa11fa04d3e747d75"
        }
    ]
}